<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mobile on Nomad&#39;s reflections</title>
    <link>rdev02.github.io/hugo-blog/tags/mobile/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Mobile on Nomad&#39;s reflections</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2010 10:37:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="rdev02.github.io/hugo-blog/tags/mobile/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>907: Invalid cod and other BlackBerry OTA problems.</title>
      <link>rdev02.github.io/hugo-blog/code/907-invalid-cod-and-other-blackberry-ota-problems/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2010 10:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>rdev02.github.io/hugo-blog/code/907-invalid-cod-and-other-blackberry-ota-problems/</guid>
      <description>&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Most of us, who developed any BlackBerry app that had to be shipped OTA had seen this &amp;#8220;descriptive&amp;#8221; error. It might be anything from invalid jad to signing problems. The one I&amp;#8217;m going to describe here is when the size of the cod file is more than 64K.
&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Finding out if you have this problem is fairly easy: just look into the final cod and see if there are actually 2 cod files packaged in one cod.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nokia Ovi suite</title>
      <link>rdev02.github.io/hugo-blog/code/nokia-ovi-suite/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2010 22:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>rdev02.github.io/hugo-blog/code/nokia-ovi-suite/</guid>
      <description>Installed, played with it a bit&amp;#8230; Looks nice 🙂
Among significant&amp;nbsp;pluses(IMHO of course):
 smoother experience nice improved and thought out UI sms log deserves additional applause (clap)(clap)(clap) back(PC-&amp;gt;phone)&amp;nbsp;synchronization&amp;nbsp;improved(both speed and reliability) working(at last) maps(NavTech)   among things I miss:     full control over the phone&amp;#8217;s file system   application install   media(other then mp3) transfer    &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;But for those the are great news: Good ol&amp;#8217; PC Suite is not removed with Ovi upgrade 🙂 So you can still use it if you wish to&amp;#8230;   &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Generally Ovi is a much better tool for daily sync then PC Suite was.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sad &amp; funny world of mobile development.</title>
      <link>rdev02.github.io/hugo-blog/code/sad-funny-world-of-mobile-development/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Dec 2009 09:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>rdev02.github.io/hugo-blog/code/sad-funny-world-of-mobile-development/</guid>
      <description>&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Being a &amp;#8216;mobile&amp;#8217;&amp;nbsp;developer is definitely fun. Although sometimes, when you think about it &amp;#8216;deeper&amp;#8217; you&amp;#8217;d rather drink a pint of whiskey:). Take a look at the enterprise Symbian OS:  http://www.codeproject.com/KB/mobile/Symbian_OS_design_faults.aspx&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;  Reliable, huh? 😉 And it&amp;#8217;s not just Symbian &amp;#8211; in my point of view it&amp;#8217;s MIDP itself. You just can&amp;#8217;t rely on it unless you test, test and once again &amp;#8211; test. For me it feels like implementation usually just do not care about about what does the specification say.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BlackBerry fun.</title>
      <link>rdev02.github.io/hugo-blog/code/blackberry-fun/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2009 14:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>rdev02.github.io/hugo-blog/code/blackberry-fun/</guid>
      <description>Reading the developers guide on BlackBerry you may come across astonishing things. I&amp;#8217;m impressed. When I started doing &amp;nbsp;little things in the blackberry app I soon got used to it and considered the platform to be well organized. Now that I&amp;#8217;m reading a book I get more and more confused about what I should do and what I shan&amp;#8217;t! Take a look at this masterpiece
 
Why it is not necessary to obfuscate applications  The compiler for the BlackBerry® Java™ Development Environment is set to minimize the size of the application.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BlackBerry internet usage, OTA and other staff.</title>
      <link>rdev02.github.io/hugo-blog/code/blackberry-internet-usage-ota-and-other-staff/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2009 11:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>rdev02.github.io/hugo-blog/code/blackberry-internet-usage-ota-and-other-staff/</guid>
      <description>Continuing the BlackBerry theme would like to share a few more issues I&amp;#8217;ve ran into recently.
 Internet usage.
If you subscribe to blackberry service you can optionally buy some &amp;#8220;internet package&amp;#8221; from your provider in order to minimize internet expenses. This a great choice since you&amp;#8217;re going to visit internet pretty often if you&amp;#8217;ve chosen blackberry. Everything goes fine until you start using Java apps on your phone. Java uses it OWN predefined internet connection DIFFERENT from the one the browser uses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BlackBerry invokeLater and Multimedia.</title>
      <link>rdev02.github.io/hugo-blog/code/blackberry-invokelater-and-multimedia/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2009 09:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>rdev02.github.io/hugo-blog/code/blackberry-invokelater-and-multimedia/</guid>
      <description>Recently had an issue in the BlackBerry Java application: it was reported to crash if the sounds were on and played often. However it didn&amp;#8217;t crash if sounds were played once in a while. After some investigation it turned out that there are no memory&amp;nbsp;leaks&amp;nbsp;but some thing blocked the event dispatch&amp;nbsp;queue. I asked for help on&amp;nbsp;Stack Overflow&amp;nbsp;and&amp;nbsp;BlackBerry developer forums&amp;nbsp;but that didn&amp;#8217;t lead me&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;anywhere except that I thought that something definitely gets locked.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Damn Symbian errors!</title>
      <link>rdev02.github.io/hugo-blog/code/damn-symbian-errors/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2009 12:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>rdev02.github.io/hugo-blog/code/damn-symbian-errors/</guid>
      <description>Now you never know how will modern technology strike you next time&amp;#8230; Experience I&amp;#8217;ve got today is remarkable. It&amp;#8217;s not that something awful happened, but potentially this is really serious. Imagine you have a template in the phone to send SMS quickly with predefined text. And Imagine this piece of software has bugs&amp;#8230; Whatever &amp;#8211; one might think if it won&amp;#8217;t send an sms &amp;#8211; I’ll retype and sent it again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>J2ME radio lists trouble</title>
      <link>rdev02.github.io/hugo-blog/code/j2me-radio-lists-trouble/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2009 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>rdev02.github.io/hugo-blog/code/j2me-radio-lists-trouble/</guid>
      <description>Recently I needed to do a simple task &amp;#8211; implement a radio button list with choices under J2ME MIDP 2.0. I started with creating an new view of type javax.microedition.lcdui.List, keeping in mind that I can just construct it with List.EXCLUSIVE and add whatever items i want and everything should work fine. Well almost&amp;#8230; All looked nice and the items showed up very attractively, having transparency and current font set up by default, which looked quite impressive.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>