<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>C&#43;&#43; on Nomad&#39;s reflections</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/c&#43;&#43;/</link>
    <description>Recent content in C&#43;&#43; on Nomad&#39;s reflections</description>
    <image>
      <title>Nomad&#39;s reflections</title>
      <url>https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/vnomad-public/blog_infra/wp_back3.jpg</url>
      <link>https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/vnomad-public/blog_infra/wp_back3.jpg</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.127.0</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Viktor Halitsyn</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2007 16:50:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/c++/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Display TIFF in picturebox (Adobe plugins)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/code/display-tiff-in-picturebox-adobe-plugins/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2007 16:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/code/display-tiff-in-picturebox-adobe-plugins/</guid>
      <description>The previous post highlighted how to accomplish the given task using TIFF-PDF-JPEG-BITMAP conversion. Though this was is complicated it works perfect. But so much code for so little functionality often is not considered good if even eccepted. Recently a new way was found. It has to be said that it is not “the proper way”, because it needs some annatural code, but it is considerably lighter than the previous one. SO the idea is to draw direktly on the window using its HWND and SDK drawContentsToFunction.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tiff to Picture box in PDF plugin ADM dialog</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/code/tiff-to-picture-box-in-pdf-plugin-adm-dialog/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2007 10:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/code/tiff-to-picture-box-in-pdf-plugin-adm-dialog/</guid>
      <description>Today i would like to continue PDF plugins development theme. The next thing i was struggling with for about three days was displaying *TIFF ot *TIF images in Picture box control on he ADMDialog. Well nice thing is it can do this, bad thing is: not the way we think it should be. Unfortunately i havent found the other way as to convert image file to JPEG format(through PDF) and that load it as BITMAP which i could put into the ADMIconRef…Also i would like to admit that after loading the HBITMAP i had to resize it to the proper the of pcture box i had.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Custom selection server in PDF plugin</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/code/custom-selection-server-in-pdf-plugin/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2007 14:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/code/custom-selection-server-in-pdf-plugin/</guid>
      <description>Recently i was developing a feature for the Adobe(R) Acrobat Reader(R) plugin and come across an issue of selecting/highlighting annotations on the document based on some criteria e.g. if an annotation is positioned too close to the margin of the page… – bad you are :). Here i’ll post a tutorial like code for atchieving this goal for when trying to resolve that problem the only helpful information i foud was the Adobe Acrobat 7.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
