<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>tools on Nomad&#39;s reflections</title>
    <link>http://blog.vnomad.com/categories/tools/</link>
    <description>Recent content in tools on Nomad&#39;s reflections</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 Nov 2017 21:37:00 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://blog.vnomad.com/categories/tools/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>CDN image hosting for blog&#39;</title>
      <link>http://blog.vnomad.com/code/2017/blog-images-using-cdn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Nov 2017 21:37:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.vnomad.com/code/2017/blog-images-using-cdn/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s rare that a blog has 0 images. Hosting them on the same box as the blog instance is the easiest solution, but it comes at a cost: disk space and page load speed. Unless you are a professional blogger, you are also not ready shell out many $$ for a CDN, so what options are there?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Migrating wordpress blog to hugo and hosting it with GitHub Pages</title>
      <link>http://blog.vnomad.com/code/2017/migrate-wordpress-to-hugo-github-pages/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2017 09:59:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.vnomad.com/code/2017/migrate-wordpress-to-hugo-github-pages/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Two weeks ago my blog was hosted on a 10$/mo vps instance in &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.digitalocean.com&#34;&gt;DigitalOcean&lt;/a&gt;, powered by a couple docker containers, running an ever dynamic &lt;a href=&#34;http://wordpress.com&#34;&gt;Wordpress&lt;/a&gt; platform. Now it&amp;rsquo;s completely static, served from &lt;a href=&#34;https://pages.github.com/&#34;&gt;GitHub Pages&lt;/a&gt; servers free. What follows is a small experience reco/guide on how to make this happen.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WISE installation studio</title>
      <link>http://blog.vnomad.com/code/wise-installation-studio/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2008 19:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.vnomad.com/code/wise-installation-studio/</guid>
      <description>Windows Installer… nightmare… WISE – hurt me plenty. Although this is much simpler and logical to my mind then WI it is still very sensible to changes. What I am trying to say – if do everything right from the first time e.g. correctly choose all names and dialogs and files e.t.c it works perfectly. But when after 5 minutes you decide to change, say, some script or file destination WISE i making so many actions in background you can’t even imagine.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
