<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ukr on Nomad&#39;s reflections</title>
    <link>blog.vnomad.com/tags/ukr/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ukr on Nomad&#39;s reflections</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Oct 2009 19:10:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="blog.vnomad.com/tags/ukr/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Flu, people and ukrainian healthcare system</title>
      <link>blog.vnomad.com/tea/flu-people-and-ukrainian-healthcare-system/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Oct 2009 19:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>blog.vnomad.com/tea/flu-people-and-ukrainian-healthcare-system/</guid>
      <description>THEY ALL SUCK!!! a big deal.
I will start with the last one. Having just recovered from the flu I decided to go to the hospital in order to check if I&amp;#8217;ve totally recovered and that there is nothing &amp;#8220;under the hood&amp;#8221; which would strike me in the back in few days. The normal procedure here is to have a blood analysis and a few more tests. Step one &amp;#8211; find the doctor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ukrainian independence day.</title>
      <link>blog.vnomad.com/tea/ukrainian-independence-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2009 19:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>blog.vnomad.com/tea/ukrainian-independence-day/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;#8217;s funny sometimes how could absolutely non-officially connected news be linked together so tightly that one couldn&amp;#8217;t even imagine. Today, reading the daily news I came across an article describing the Barack Obama&amp;#8217;s attitude towards Ukrainian sovereignty along with greetings regarding this year&amp;#8217;s independence day. Between the other it was stated there that &amp;#8220;USA won&amp;#8217;t abandon Ukraine on its way towards democratic future&amp;#8230;&amp;#8221;. Nice words, always pleased to hear/read such things in the mediapress.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ukrainians on Times.</title>
      <link>blog.vnomad.com/tea/ukrainians-on-times/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2009 19:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>blog.vnomad.com/tea/ukrainians-on-times/</guid>
      <description>Today visited Times. Was interested in one article about (RU+GBR)/UA. To hell the article. I read the comments. OMG.
 OMG again.   &amp;#8220;People, even something that you care for most (democracy?) does not give you the right to lie passionately and ignore facts and invent lies. BTW, Eduard Glushko &amp;#8211; if you are so much afraid of the The Molotov-Ribbentrop Pact, it still can be repaired. Poland has to give back to Germany the territories they got after WW2.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>