<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Travel on Nomad&#39;s reflections</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/categories/travel/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Travel on Nomad&#39;s reflections</description>
    <image>
      <title>Nomad&#39;s reflections</title>
      <url>https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/vnomad-public/blog_infra/wp_back3.jpg</url>
      <link>https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/vnomad-public/blog_infra/wp_back3.jpg</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.127.0</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Viktor Halitsyn</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 Mar 2023 06:17:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/categories/travel/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>TRVL: Japan. Skiing, Tokyo and Kyoto</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/travel/2023/japan_ski/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Mar 2023 06:17:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/travel/2023/japan_ski/</guid>
      <description>It started as an innocent idea concluding my 2022 Canada ski trip: what if we went to Japan for ski trip, instead of Canada? Indeed, sometimes the border crossing and car travel time would amount to a length of a direct SEA-&amp;gt;HND. Japan was locked for travel at the time and we decided to commit to it softly, putting little hope on this actually coming to fruition.
jumping ahead, a piece of contemporary japanese art Lo and behold: mid 2022 fall Japan has re-opened for tourism and the place we booked for stay did not go out of business because of Covid.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turkey vacation.</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/travel/tur/turkey-vacation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Sep 2009 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/travel/tur/turkey-vacation/</guid>
      <description>Amazing. Yes it was really amazing. I traveled with my darling Anya and I didn&amp;amp;#8217;t expect it that good especially keeping in mind that we had to go with a 4 star hotel. However it was really nice and if you consider going to Turkey with a low budget &amp;amp;#8211; I would recommend [Kosdere Exclusive][1](the place we stayed in). First thing I have to mention is our tour agency [Tez Tour][2].</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>X-ray headphones improve</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/travel/x-ray-headphones-improve/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Apr 2009 18:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/travel/x-ray-headphones-improve/</guid>
      <description>I had to travel to Sweden recently. So probably in 2 hours or so i packed all the necessary things, took my old notebook-bag out of the dusty closet (cleaned it) and packed all the NB-stuff into it. I also included my new KOSS UR-40 headphones in the bag. I have to tell I wasn’tso much impressed when I bought them. You know – in Ukraine if want to know how smth sounds you’ll probably have to buy it first.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
